《小鬼当家3》
(香港)
有顾客出一千万买导弹芯片
Ten million dollars for the missile chip.
不是计划..
Not a plan..
是真正的芯片
..but the chip itself.
为何出那么高价?
Why the big price?
我的顾客肯出钱买
My clients have requested it.
我便照客户的吩咐去做
I honor my clients' requests.
看来你的客户
Sounds like your clients..
想制造雷达探测不到的导弹
..want to build a missile that can't be detected by radar.
我不问顾客作何用途,博普雷先生
I don't ask questions, Mr.Beaupre.
不过谁拥有这芯片,就能控制整个地区
But whoever possesses this chip could dominate the entire region.
(AXUS国防科技公司)
(加州 硅谷)
- 晚安,乔治 - 晚安,库珀先生
- Good night, George. - Good night, Mr.Cooper.
- 没武器 - 给
- He's clean. - Here.
你要的货
That's what you asked for.
空军NSB-100,C系列
Air Force NSB-100, C series.
只要装在导弹上,空中防御系统便无法抵御
If that goes in a missile, air defenses can't stop it.
听着,我要赶飞机
Look, I got a plane to catch.
我的钱呢?
Where's my money?
给
Here.
藏在玩具车内
Hide it in the toy car.
我们可以通过机场安检
We'll slip it right past airport security.
我们走
Let's go.
欢迎到旧金山国际机场
Welcome to San Francisco International Airport.
请小心保管行李
Do not leave your bags unattended.
请将首饰取下
Please remove your jewelry.
是的,女士
Yes, ma'am.
我们走
Let's go.
女士,你得等等
Ma'am, you have to wait.
谢谢
Thank you.
下一位
Next, please.
哦,我的天
Oh, my God.
(离境航班资料)
让开.让开!
Move. Move!
年轻人!
Young man!
我查过达拉斯,迈阿密,纽约和丹佛候机室,找不到
The Dallas, Miami, New York and Denver lounges. Nothing.
酒吧,餐厅,俱乐部都没有
Bars, restaurants, club lounge, clean.
厕所也没有
When I was in the john, I didn't see anything in there.
一定在飞机上
It has to be on a plane.
(登机)
(芝加哥)
我们去芝加哥
We are going to Chicago.
冬天去那里?
In the winter?
我带了夏天衣物
I packed tropical.
欢迎光临芝加哥,室外气温华氏29度
Welcome to Chicago, where it's 29 degrees outside.
欢迎光临芝加哥
Welcome to Chicago.
再见
Bye-bye.
来,先生
Here you go, sir.
博普雷先生!
Mr.Beaupre!
昂格尔先生,杰尼根先生
Mr.Unger, Mr.Jernigan.
借过..
Excuse me.
- 借过 - 让开
- Out of my way. - Move.
- 你有行李吗,女士? - 没有,快走!
- Did you check any bags, ma'am? - No. Floor it!
她走了
She's leaving.
嘿!
Hey!
是他
That's him.
对不起,老伯.我能问你件事吗?
Excuse me, pop. Can I ask you something?
什么?
What?
1月8日下午4点20分,你从机场接了一位客人
You had a fare from the airport around 16:20 hours, January 8.
是一位白人老太太
Senior citizen, female, Caucasian.
- 什么? - 今天大约4点30,载了老太婆
- What? - About 4:30 today. Old broad.
- 哦,对 - 你记得地址吗?
- Oh, yeah. - You got an address on that?
北丹佛公园,华盛顿街
North Devon Park, Washington Street.
请形容一下房子
Describe the house, please.
宏伟,古老
Big, old..
中古型房子
..Tudor-like place.
- 详细一点 - 有圣诞灯,门上有彩环
- Details. - Christmas lights, wreath on the door.
车道尾有圣诞树,那个车道..
Christmas tree by the driveway, and the driveway..
是那个街区唯一没铲雪的
..was the only one on the block not shoveled.
我做完了,赫斯太太.我又热又累..
I'm done, Mrs.Hess. I'm exhausted and sweaty..
..但因为我衣服太厚你看不见
..but you can't see because I'm covered up.
你应及时清雪
You were to deal with the snow promptly.
- 是的,不过.. - 不用找借口了
- Yes, but.. - "Buts" are for ashtrays.
我不想听借口.我们早就说好了,你没守约
I don't care for excuses. We had an understanding and you broke it.
- 你的话不可信 - 对不起,这次免费吧,赫斯太太
- Your word is worthless. - Sorry. That'll be no charge, Mrs.Hess.
所以你好告诉邻居我占你便宜?
So you can tell the neighbors I stiffed you on a job?
这是旧金山著名的酸面包?
Is this a loaf of the famous San Francisco sourdough bread?
这不能做很好吃的三明治,是吧?
This won't make a very tasty sandwich, will it?
因为有个莽撞的笨蛋拿了我的袋子..
Because of some silly, inconsiderate boob who took my bag..
使我的面包留在旧金山!
..I left my bread in San Francisco!
对不起,赫斯太太,但我想我差不多,可能..
Pardon me, Mrs.Hess, but I think I'm almost, maybe..
也许,也许会赶不及吃晚饭
..possibly, probably gonna be late for my dinner.
拿去当作酬劳,我没有用
Consider this your payment. I have no use for it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你母亲有没有教你..
And have your mother teach you..
在女士面前抓痒是不礼貌的
..that it is rude to scratch yourself in front of a lady.
晚安,艾历克斯
Good night, Alex.
哎..
Jeez.
真麻烦
What a grouch.
全部都是旧房子
They're all old..
大多是中古型
..most of them are Tudor..
门口都有花圈与圣诞树
..all have wreaths and Christmas trees..
雪都铲走了
..and the snow's all shoveled.
共有14户
There are 14 houses.
玩具车一定在其中一家
The toy car must be in one of them.
我们要全部搜
We'll have to search them all.
- 我们白天再来 - 我们大白天偷入屋?
- We'll come back when it's light. - We're gonna work in daylight?
这里是郊区,昂格尔先生
It's the suburbs, Mr.Unger.
白天没人在家
Nobody's home during the day.
(艾历克斯·普鲁伊特科学展览室)
吃吧,小飞鱼
There you go, Speedy.
查理,我去年就告诉过你,我现在再告诉你..
Charlie, I told you last year, and I'm telling you now..
我周末不能上班
..I can't work weekends.
- 为什么不行? - 我有三个孩子和丈夫
- Why not? - I've got three kids and a husband.
那是玛丽·卢,她的生活只有工作
That's Mary Lou. She has no life.
那就是说她周末上班没问题,但我不能
It means nothing to her to work weekends, but I can't.
我的房子装修到一半,我的孩子们有活动
My house is half-renovated. My kids have activities.
他们不想父母只懂工作
They need to see us doing more than running to the car.
电话上我解释不清楚我们为什么对这个产品这样期待
I can't really explain over the phone why we're so excited about this product.
好吧,你确定周三会到?
Okay, will you sure be here on Wednesday?
对,我周三到克里夫兰
Right, I'll be in Cleveland on Wednesday.
对,周三,我们到时面对面谈
Yeah, Wednesday. We'll talk about it then. Face to face.
直截了当
Man to man.
对,直截了当
Yeah, man to man.
(艾历克斯的财产)
你弟弟的昆虫!
Your brother's bug!
小心!小心!
Careful! Careful!
正中红心!
Bull's-eye!
三分球
Three from downtown.
观众欢呼若狂
And the crowd goes wild.
哦,天
Oh, man.
我希望他们不是..
I hope they're not..
艾历克斯那小东西又给厕板压痛!
Alex slammed the seat down on his thing again!
正中红心
Bull's-eye.
艾历克斯,怎么回事?
Alex, what happened?
跟我没关系,我是无辜的!
I had nothing to do with it. I'm innocent!
我得走了.我孩子的小东西又给厕板压痛
I gotta go. My kid slammed the seat on his thing again.
我们再联络
I'll call you back.
艾历克斯?
Alex?
含在口里
Keep that in your mouth.
水痘
Chickenpox.
妈妈,请恕我说一句
Mom, with all due respect..
他那昆虫死了,所以诈病不交作业
..this is to get out of his science project because his bug died.
什么?
What?
- 他脸上的水痘不是很严重 - 身上长满水痘
- His face doesn't look that bad. - His body's covered.
- 屁股有吗? - 闭嘴!
- Would that include his buttocks? - Shut up!
太好了.如果留下抓痕,我们就叫他痘皮屁股
This is great. If he scratches his spots, we can call him scar-butt.
- 出去 - 再见
- Leave. - Goodbye.
- 我煮汤给你喝 - 我把电视搬来给你
- I'll make you some soup. - I'll bring the TV up.
真遗憾
I'm so sorry.
嘿,别抓水痘
Hey. Don't scratch.
含在舌头下,我就回来
Keep that under your tongue. I'll be back.
快乐家庭..对吗,多丽丝?
Nice family. Huh, Doris?
- 你们该走了 - 回头见,爸爸
- You guys should get going. - See you later, Dad.
格林菲尔德投资EAFA基金40万
Greenfield's 401 k is in the Effa fund.
你是中小型基金,这正是您短缺的地方
You have it in the Midcap fund. That's where your 3,000 shortfall is.
请等一等
I have to put you on hold one sec.
艾历克斯,我跟公司通话!
Alex, I'm on with the office!
所以我认为我们..
So I think that what we..
- 抱歉,我能一会儿再打给你吗? - 当然
- I'm sorry. Can I call you back in a minute? - Sure.
射中
Gotcha.
你叫我?
You rang?
口渴?
Thirsty?
谢谢,妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
- 就是这里 - 真希望我丈夫今天能来
- Here we are. - I wish my husband could be here.
这里很舒适
It's a cozy little place.
很不错!
Isn't this charming!
随时可以交付
And it's available immediately.
我的孩子会很喜欢
My boys are just gonna love it here.
嗯,一定很喜欢
Yes, they will.
(出租)
另外,特别的照顾和喂养,会让你的宠物值得夸耀
Plus, special care and feeding tips, next on Pets on Parade.
看,多丽丝
Look, Doris.
要是你觉得很过瘾,好戏还在后头
If you think that was amusing, wait till you see what I do next.
哦,对
Oh, yeah.
- 坐下! - 下周会很精彩
- Sit! - I can't wait for next week.
我讨厌狗
I hate dogs.
查理,我们谈过的.你知道我不能去.艾历克斯病了
Charlie, we've been over on this. You know I can't come in. Alex is sick.
梅林要审查这个建议
Melling's reviewing the proposal.
- 你开玩笑 - 不
- You're kidding. - No.
- 他来多久? - 星期五走
- How long's he in town? - He's leaving Friday.
- 我们不能取消 - 没关系
- We can't cancel. - It's okay.
- 玛丽·卢能办妥 - 那不是他要找的人
- Mary Lou can handle it. - She's not who he expects to see.
你是关键人物.你答应我会处理的
You're the point person. You told me you'd handle it.
我知道,我答应过你,但那时我孩子没生病
I know, I primised you, but my child wasn't sick when I promised you..
不能找人照顾孩子吗?
Not my fault you can't find a sitter.
好吧,好.一小时.我只能去一小时
Okay, fine. One hour. I can come in for one hour. That is it.
若艾历克斯找我,我就走,就算开除我,我也得走
If Alex beeps me, I'm gone and you can fire me if you want to, but I'm gone.
凯伦..
Karen..
查理,你令我很难做,要我在赚钱..
Charlie, you're making me choose between making a house payment..
与照顾生病的孩子中选择,令我十分不满
..and taking care of my sick child and I don't appreciate it.
讨厌
Jerk.
你告诉过查理我病得很重吗?
You tell Charlie I'm desperately ill?
谢谢你,艾历克斯
Thank you, Alex.
对,查理知道你病了
Yes, he knows you're sick.
家庭年假呢?
What about the Family Leave Act?
我只去办点事
I just have to go in..
签些文件,露露面
..sign some papers and show my face.
我最多只去一小时
I'll be gone an hour at the very most.
我打电话给赫斯太太,告诉她你一个人在家..
I called Mrs.Hess and told her you're alone..
你打给赫斯太太了?她知道我一个人在家?
You called Mrs.Hess? She knows I'll be alone?
她说如果有事,她会过来帮忙
She said if anything comes up, she'll be right over.
- 她虽然不高兴但.. - 她会过来给我抽烟
- She wasn't happy about it.. - She'll come over and make me smoke cigarette.
- 别胡说 - 如果有龙卷风怎办?
- Don't be ridiculous. - What if there's a tornado?
冬天没龙卷风
They don't have any in winter.
- 暴动呢? - 不会有的
- Social unrest? - I don't think so.
无聊?我听说是老人死因之一
Boredom? I heard it's deadly in old folks.
再见,亲爱的
Goodbye, sweetie.
如果有窃贼呢?
What about crooks?
白天不会有窃贼
That's not a problem during the day.
为什么不会?白天家里没人
Why not? No one's home during the day.
我是小孩子也知道白天有机可乘
I'm 8 and I figured that out.
那些成年窃贼想不到吗?
Couldn't a grown-up crook figure it out too?
这社区很安全,只有一条路出入
This is a very safe neighborhood. There's only one road in and out.
我会锁门,你有我的电话
The doors'll be locked, you have my numbers.
- 我尽快回来 - 可是,妈妈!
- I'll be home soon. - But, Mom!
要是恐龙,巨型蜘蛛,木乃伊,僵尸..
What about dragons, giant spiders, mummies, the living dead..
还有其他东西出来呢?
..and other figments of my imagination?
艾历克斯,我帮不了你
Alex, I can't help you there.
只有你能控制幻觉
Only you can control your imagination.
自己吓自己
That's a scary thought.
真奇怪
That's weird.
哦,我的天
Oh, my God.
20秒后出来
20 seconds out.
没人
Clear.
报案电话
911 Emergency.
- 我看见一个窃贼! - 你一人在家?
- I saw a burglar! - Are you by yourself?
我妈妈要出门一下,我长水痘
My mom had to leave. I have the chickenpox.
你地址是哪里?
Can I have your address?
窃贼不在我家!是在史蒂芬斯家!
He's not at my house! He's at the Stephans'!
他们地址是华盛顿街3015号
Their address is 3015 Washington Street!
没有
Nothing.
史蒂芬斯家有盗贼!我用望远镜看到的!
Burglar at the Stephans'! I saw him with my telescope!
有个带着狗的女人,灰色货车,还有穿运动装的男人!
There's a woman with a dog and a gray van, and a man in running clothes!
我只认得那只狗,像是强尼·艾伦的狗
I didn't recognize anyone, but the dog looked like Johnny Allen's..
所以我了报警
..so I called the police.
你报警了?
You called the police?
冻死了!
Freeze!
防盗警铃开了,没有坏
The burglar alarm was on and working.
屋子里面没人
There was no one in the house.
好像没有什么东西被偷走
Doesn't appear that anything's been taken.
我不知道他看见什么,但屋里没人
I don't know what he saw but it wasn't a person.
非常抱歉
I'm very sorry about this.
我儿子长水痘,我必须去上班,拿些文件
My son's been home with chickenpox and I had to run to work to pick up some papers.
情非得已,我通常不会这样
I'm strapped. I don't normally do this.
孩子,报假案不是闹着玩的
Son, false alarms are no joking matter.
不是报假案!
It wasn't a false alarm!
屋里那贼人有两人在外把风,还有辆灰色的车
The guy in the house had two lookouts and a driver in a gray van.
他有点发烧
He's been running a fever.
教他报警是严重的事
Ours is a serious business.
哦,他知道,我们圣诞节送他警察玩具
Oh, he knows. We gave him a police set for Christmas..
不是今年,是去年.你知道,警徽,警帽,警笛
Not this one, but last. You know, one with a badge, a hat and a whistle.
他很认真,还在屋内捉人
He took it very seriously. He arrested relatives for various crimes.
不是重罪,没放回厕板或打鼾..
Not real crimes, but for leaving the toilet seat up and snoring and..
好
Absolutely.
我会教他,谢谢
I will, yes. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你上床去
You get in that bed.
对不起,我看到有人在凯伦·史蒂芬斯的卧室
Excuse me, I saw a man in Karen Stephans' bedroom.
白种男性,比爸爸大一点,戴检查屁股的手套
A white male a little older than Dad, wearing butt inspection gloves.
我早警告你别看望远镜
I warned you about that telescope.
看久了会产生幻觉,不管是不是有人
Look long enough and you'll see things, whether or not they're there.
要到35岁后才有人相信你
I guess you have to be 35 before anyone listens to you.
别耍小聪明,艾历克斯.就算你生病,我还是很生气
Don't get smart with me, Alex. Sick or not, I'm very angry with you.
你今天搞很多事
You caused a lot of trouble today.
爸爸和我得去修史蒂芬斯家的门.你觉得这样我们很高兴?
Dad and I have to replace a door at Stephans'. You think we're happy about it?
我确实看到
I saw what I saw.
彼得·博普雷
Peter Beaupre..
厄尔·昂格尔
..Earl Unger..
伯顿·杰尼根
..Burton Jernigan..
爱丽丝·里文斯
..and Alice Rivens.
他们用化名但没上香港的班机
They were ticketed under aliases but didn't board the Hong Kong flight.
我相信他们还在美国,除此之外,一无所知
I believe they're still in the U.S., but beyond that, I don't know.
女士们先生们..
Ladies and gentlemen..
我们必须找回那芯片
..we've got to find that chip.
警铃有什么问题?
What went wrong with the burglar alarm?
- 没什么,不是因为警铃 - 那谁会报警?
- Nothing. It wasn't the alarm. - Then who called the police?
杰尼根先生,你猜呢?
Mr.Jernigan, care to speculate?
有车经过,邮差来过
Cars came and went. The mailman came by.
到处都可能有人看见,可能是任何人
We could have a watcher on any house. It could be anybody.
不是普通人,一定是住这条街的
I don't think it's just anybody. I think it's someone on our street.
某个我们没注意到的人
Someone we are not tracking.
我们遗漏的对象
Someone we've missed.
爸爸,计程车来了
Dad, cab's here.
哦,糟糕
Oh, shoot.
妈妈还没回来
Mom's not back yet.
呃,好吧
Well, all right.
妈妈拿文件去银行
Mom took some documents to the bank.
她不会去很久的
She can't be gone more than a few minutes.
赫斯太太在家,你别担心
Mrs.Hess is home. You'll be fine.
我的传呼号码快拨键电话上有
My beeper's on speed dial.
- 2键,妈妈在1键 - 对
- Second button. Mom's is the first. - Right.
- 那,你没事? - 绝对没事
- So, you're okay? - Positively.
亲我一下
Give me a kiss.
爸爸
Dad.
这社区很安全
This is a safe neighborhood.
警察很能干,你昨天见过
We have great police, as you learned yesterday.
不会发生什么事的
Nothing bad will happen to you.
- 爸爸? - 怎么?
- Dad? - Yeah?
- 机票拿了? - 是的
- Got your tickets? - Yep.
- 钱包呢? - 在我口袋里
- Got your wallet? - It's in my pocket.
你的口袋在哪里?
Where's your pocket?
嗯
Yeah.
- 谢谢 - 再见,爸爸
- Thank you. - Bye, Dad.
她出门了
She's leaving.
3025号没人
3025 is all clear.
红色箱式车往南行
Red sedan heading south.
转右,停
Turning right. Hold.
- 你及时赶上,普鲁伊特先生 - 等等,等等
- You are just in time, Mr.Pruitt. - Wait, wait.
哦,不
Oh, no.
太好了
Yes.
放弃行动.放弃
Abort. Abort.
撤离,我来处理
Evacuate the area. I'm way my own.
走!
Let's go!
快!快!
Move! Move!
好极了!
Cool!
检查后面
Check the back.
没人
Nothing.
我们去楼上看看
Let's check upstairs.
贼在哪里?
Where's the burglar?
没有贼
There is no burglar.
只是生病在家的小孩报假案
Just a kid home sick from school, making false alarms.
真不好意思
How embarrassing.
这是你两天内第二次报警
This is the second time in two days that you've called the police.
报警是很严重的事
It's a very serious matter when a person calls the police.
我昨天看到有贼,今天又看到
I saw a burglar yesterday, and I saw one today.
艾历克斯,听警官说
Alex, listen to the chief.
- 那屋里没人 - 强尼·艾伦的狗呢?
- There was no one in that house. - What about Johnny Allen's dog?
我昨晚问过强尼.他的狗周一早上被绑架了
I talked to Johnny last night. His dog was kidnapped Monday morning.
他看见了?
Did he see it happen?
艾历克斯,快道歉,然后回你房间
Alex, apologize to the chief and go up to your room.
做好市民也要挨骂
Excuse me for being a good citizen.
艾历克斯!很抱歉
Alex! I'm very sorry.
不会再发生的
This will not happen again.
对吗,亲爱的?真的,我保证
Will it, honey? Really, I promise you.
我们不是不准他报警..
We wouldn't want to discourage him from calling us..
而是真的有事时才报警
..in the event that something real ever does happen.
讨厌鬼
Loser.
- 闭嘴 - 来啊
- Shut up. - Make me.
你已烦了警察两次,留下记录
You pranked them twice. It's on your permanent record.
以后你一辈子,如果你报警求助,警察也不会来救你
For your whole life, if you call for help, it won't come.
- 爸爸错过了飞机 - 他跟他老板开会迟到
- Dad missed his plane. - He was late to meet his boss.
我们还要付血汗钱给史蒂芬斯家
We have to give family cash to the Stephans..
给那个邪恶老人去修他们的门
..and to an evil octogenarian to repair their doors.
更糟的是..
And even worse..
我们成为大笑柄
The world laughs.
你让全家丢脸
You've stained the family name.
先是史蒂芬斯家
First the Stephans.
然后到赫斯太太
Then Mrs.Hess.
我同意,多丽丝.下个就是奥尔考茨家
I agree, Doris. The next stop is the Alcotts' house.
进屋不偷东西,究竟是什么贼?
What burglar goes into a house and doesn't take anything?
你知道我怎么想吗?他们一定在找什么特别的东西
You know what I think? They're looking for something special.
他们去每家找因为他们不知道在谁家
And they're looking in every house because they don't know who has it.
问题是..
The question is..
在找什么?
..what is it?
如果没人设法阻止
If nobody's gonna do anything about this..
我只好靠自己了
..I'll just have to do it myself.
抱歉,我还没睡醒
I am so sorry. I'm clearly not awake.
没关系
It's all right.
开心点
Have a nice day.
希望
I'll try.
留心看
Watch this.
看,多丽丝
Look, Doris.
我忘了有楼梯
I forgot about the stairs.
是他了,多丽丝,是他了
Got him, Doris. Got him.
对,对,对!
Yes, yes, yes!
一定要捉到你
You are so busted.
找到了
I have it.
玩具车.在拍摄我
The toy car. It's videotaping me.
再说一遍
Come back on that.
冲啊!快!快!快!
Come on! Go! Go! Go!
别打转!
Don't spin!
喂,你!
You there!
你待我不错,我没必要杀你
You was friendly. I don't have to kill you.
那笔钱不属于你
You got money that doesn't belong to you.
你退后.不关你的事
Now you back off. Not your business.
你好,我是凯伦.嗨,怎么样?
Hello, this is Karen. Hi, how's it going?
我回办公室又迟了
I'm running late for the office again.
我觉得蓝筹股价太高
I think blue chips are overvalued.
科枝股不错
Technology stocks are good.
我在洗澡,能待会儿打给你吗?
I'm in the shower. Can I call you back?
"坏,坏勒罗伊·布朗"
Bad, bad Leroy Brown
"全城最坏的猫"
Baddest cat in the whole damn town
"坏过老金刚"
Badder than old King Kong
"贱过丧家犬"
Meaner than a junkyard dog
加油,加油
Come on, come on.
再见!
See you!
车在外面,屋内有女人.快过来!
The car's outside. I got the woman here. Get over here!
快点,起来!
Come on, get up!
大家都在赶时间
Everybody's in a hurry.
是摄像机.有人在监视我们
It's a camera. Someone's onto us.
怎样?芯片在车上,我们45分钟后到机场
Think it matters? Chip's in the car. We're at the airport in 45 minutes.
爱丽丝在哪儿?
Where is Alice?
怎么回事?
What happened?
屋内有女人.我去解决她
There is a woman in the house. I'll deal with her.
拿芯片
Get the chip.
我去追
I got it.
女士
Ma'am?
能跟你谈谈吗?
May I have a word with you?
别进来,我没穿衣服
Don't come in. I'm naked.
你打什么主意,猴子屁股?
What's on your mind, monkey butt?
来吧
Come on.
什么臭味?
What's that funky smell?
车子不见了
I lost it.
什么?
What?!
快点,快,快,快!
Come on, go, go, go!
超出了摇控范围!
It's out of range!
拿到了
I got it.
我看到了
I see it.
小心
Look out.
杰尼根,往哪个方向?
Jernigan, which direction?
刚经过,往南方朝亚当斯街去
It got past me. It's heading south on Adams.
我紧追其后
I'm right behind the little..
离开马路,穿过后院..
It's off the street, going through back yards..
往西走
..heading west.
爱丽丝,你在哪里?
Alice, what's your position?
第四间屋,正向小巷走
Fourth house. Moving to the alley.
我看到了
I see it.
穿过篱笆
It's going through the hedge.
杰尼根,车在哪儿?
Jernigan, position.
在你那里
You're there.
- 看到了! - 看到了!
- I got it! - I got it!
昂格尔.你在哪儿?
Unger. What's your position?
往华盛顿街
Heading down Washington Street.
我没听到,哪里?
I didn't copy. Where?
我说..我朝华..
I said, I'm heading to Wa..
停车,你个笨蛋!
Stop, you nitwit!
车不见了
I don't see anything.
我去找找
I'll look around.
还没找到
I don't have it yet.
我们没时间了,放弃吧
We're out of time. Give it up.
他们拿了录影带,为什么还追玩具车?
They got the tape. Why'd they still chase the toy car?
车又不贵
It's not that expensive.
他们肯定没时间没空玩遥控车
I'm sure they don't have enough time to play with it.
(美国空军招聘中心)
看,多丽丝
Look, Doris.
(空军募兵处)
电脑芯片?你在哪里找到的?
Computer chip, huh? Where'd you find it?
在遥控车里,赫斯太太送我的
In a remote-control car I got for shoveling snow for Mrs.Hess.
她住在对面街
She lives across the street.
上面写着美国空军..
It says U.S. Air Force..
但你得要用放大镜才看得见
..but you have to look under a magnifying glass to see.
孩子,很多玩具都有空军的编号
Kid, a lot of toys have "Air Force" written on it.
这里是征兵办公室,我们不管这些事
This is a recruiting office. We don't handle this.
我能告诉你芯片编号,你找人替我查查吗?
Can I give you the chip number to give to the right guys?
你觉得我们要告诉妈妈芯片的事吗?
You think we should tell Mom about the chip?
你说得对,大人知道得越少越好
I guess you're right. The less they know, the better.
他们不是好人
Those guys are bad news.
多谢你用车撞我
I can't tell you how much I appreciate you hitting me with the van.
别义气用事
Never let emotions get the best of you.
你该提高警觉
You should have been more vigilant.
你该去上驾驶课
You should have taken driver's ed.
是小孩,一定是小孩
It's a kid. It has to be a kid.
我老了膝盖痛,全怪杰尼根
I'm gonna have bad knees when I'm old. I'll have Jernigan to thank.
警察来了两次,他们不相信那孩子..
The cops come twice, they don't believe him..
所以他自己调查
..he takes matters into his own hands.
没有别的可能
It can't be anything else.
果真如此,我说我们没其他办法
If that's the case, I say take no chances.
明天,把附近小孩全杀了.干掉他们
Tomorrow, whack every kid in the neighborhood. Burn them.
然后再找玩具车
Then look for that stupid car.
我一直觉得3026号有问题
My thoughts keep turning to number 3026.
玩具车在那附近打转
It's within the operating radius of the toy car.
那里能看到所有的屋子
It's in sight of all the houses.
- 喂? - 你拿到芯片了吗?
- Hello? - Do you have the missile chip?
快到手了
We are close.
如果24小时内没拿到的话,博普雷先生
If I don't have the chip in 24 hours, Mr.Beaupre..
我将中止行动
..I will have to terminate the mission..
除掉所有参与行动的人
..and nullify all the participants.
你明白吗?
You understand, don't you?
爸爸明晚回家
Dad's home tomorrow night.
我12点到5点要开会,所以我要你和莫莉..
I have my meeting from 12 till 5, so I need you and Molly..
你们放学后直接回家陪艾历克斯
..to come straight home after school to stay with Alex.
不行,不可能.我有体操课
I can't. No way. Impossible. I have gymnastics.
- 我要打曲棍球 - 要我再说一次吗?
- I have hockey. - Do I need to repeat myself?
我想你可以找赫斯太太
I thought you were getting Mrs.Hess.
对,她比我和斯坦有责任感多了
Yeah, she's a lot more responsible than me and Stan.
赫斯太太是后备
Mrs.Hess is a backup.
除非有急事,我真的不想打扰她
Unless it's an emergency, I really don't want to call her.
我会照顾自己
I'll be fine by myself.
问题解决
There you have it. Settled.
请传"假案"给我好吗?
Alex, could you pass me the false alarms?
对不起.抱歉,我是说给我豆
Excuse me. Sorry, I meant the peas.
喂?
Hello?
哦,嗨
Oh, hi.
对.他出水痘呆在家里
Yeah. He's been home with the chickenpox.
艾历克斯,你认识布拉德利·克洛维斯吗?
Alex, do you know a Bradley Clovis?
认识
Yeah.
是他妈妈.你拿了他的玩具车吗?
It's his mom. Did you take a toy car from him?
他有摇控车,但那是邻居送的
He has one of those cars, but he got it from a neighbor.
找到了
We have it.
艾历克斯,你干什么?你不能挂断我电话
Alex, what is the matter with you? You don't disconnect my calls.
不要跟克洛维斯太太谈
Don't talk to Mrs.Clovis.
- 为什么? - 她很危险
- Why not? - She's dangerous.
- 你在说些什么? - 她说谎
- What are you talking about? - It was lies.
全是谎话.那不是她
They're all lies. It wasn't her.
你什么意思,那不是她?
What do you mean, it wasn't her?
打给她,你会吓一跳
Call her, you'll be surprised.
打出电话
Outgoing call.
转接
Rerouted.
你好,克洛维斯家
Hello, Clovis'.
- 抱歉,我们.. - 抱歉
- I beg your pardon. We just.. - I'm sorry.
我挂断了你电话,凯伦?
Did I disconnect you, Karen?
不,是我.我们家里装修,电话线失常
No, it was me. We're renovating, the phone lines are a mess.
他们拦截电话
They intercepted the phone call.
听着,我不是指控你儿子偷东西
Listen, I didn't mean to accuse your son.
一定是布拉德利把玩具车乱放
I'm certain Bradley just misplaced his toy car.
小孩子,他们找不到就以为被偷了
Kids. They lose something and assume it's been stolen.
小男孩想像力丰富,对吗?
Little boys do have wild imaginations, don't they?
是的,没错
Yes, they do.
他们明天会来抓我,多丽丝.没人相信我
They're gonna come after me tomorrow, Doris. Nobody will listen.
无论我父母或者莫莉或者斯坦..
Not my parents or Molly or Stan..
或者警察还是空军.没有人
..or the police or the Air Force. Nobody.
那,我怎么办?
So, what do I do?
要我躲起来?不行
If that means hide, you're wrong.
要我反击?对了
If that means fight, you're right.
我捉到他们时,大人就明白,知道我说的是真话
They'll understand when I'm done, and know I was telling the truth.
我不会哭,难过或害怕
I'm not gonna cry of feel sad or scared.
他们是成年罪犯
They're grown-up criminals..
但这是我地盘,这是我的家
..but this is my neighborhood and this is my house.
不管他们多大,多强壮
No matter how old they are, no matter how big they are..
都不能在这里打倒我.他们不能在我家打倒我
..they can't beat me here. They can't beat me at home.
要收买我闭嘴吗?两片,否则免谈
Want to buy a little silence? Double or nothing.
(意大利粉肉酱)
芝加哥地区将有大风雪
We're watching a major storm bearing down on Chicago.
在雷达上,你可以看见风雪越来越大
On the radar, you can see the snow is increasing in intensity.
暴风雪预报
Heavy snow is forecasted.
居民请尽可能留在家中
Residents are urged to stay indoors if possible.
接近目标
Approaching target.
没人
All clear.
开战了,多丽丝
Here we go, Doris.
不,站住!
No, stop!
首先,我们要释放人质
First, we free the hostages.
打开光纤摄影机
Switching on the fiber optics.
艾历克斯,你能去开下门吗?
Alex, can you get the door?
没人应门
No answer.
目标人物真的没离开?
Are we certain target has not left?
我们会看到的
We would've seen.
我重覆,没人应门
I repeat, there is no movement inside.
能否进去?
Permission to enter.
爱丽丝?
Alice?
嘿,回家去.回家去
Hey. Go home. Go home.
我需要支援.我曝光了
I need assistance. I'm exposed.
留在原处
Maintain your position.
不要,我重覆,别轻举妄动
Do not, I repeat, do not draw attention to yourself.
去接她
Pick her up.
等暴风雪降临再来,让风雪遮掩我们行踪
We'll move in after the storm hits, let Mother Nature cover our tracks.
刚从空军那里收到
This just came in from the Air Force.
有个叫普鲁伊特的小孩联络芝加哥招聘中心
Some kid named Pruitt called the recruiting office in Chicago.
说他在玩具车中找到芯片
Said he found a computer chip in a toy car.
我们去芝加哥
We're going to Chicago.
你看了气象预报吗?
Did you watch the weather?
- 是的.没问题,外套在那里 - 谢谢,我要穿咖啡色的
- Yeah. No problems. Your coat's there. - Thanks. I want to wear my brown one.
等等!
Wait!
不如你去泡一杯咖啡,我帮你拿外套
Go fill your commuter cup with coffee and I'll get your coat for you.
谢谢,亲爱的
Thanks, hon.
我帮你做三明治
I'll make you a sandwich.
- 你的外套 - 谢谢
- Here's your coat. - Thanks.
亲爱的,这星期很抱歉
Sweetheart, I'm sorry about this week.
忙忙碌碌的真不开心.不该这样的
It breaks my heart to have to come and go. It shouldn't be this way.
没关系,不关你的事.身不由己而已
It's okay. It's not you. It's the times.
谢谢,亲爱的
Thanks, hon.
你有传呼机?
You have your beeper?
有
Yeah.
很好.每半小时联络一次
Great. I'll call every half-hour.
整天都会跟你保持联络
I'll go online and keep the connection open all day.
开会时也带着手提电脑
I'll have my laptop in all my meetings.
我们随时保持联络
We'll be in contact at all times.
我带着移动电话,你有我的传真号码
I have my cellular. You've got my fax number.
我们保持连线
We're wired.
哦,我的天啊.克洛维斯太太来过电话吗?
Oh, my gosh. Did Mrs.Clovis call?
她说要看车是不是布拉德利的
She was gonna stop by to confirm that Bradley's name wasn't on the car.
你洗澡时她来过
She did when you were in the shower.
- 你给她看了? - 当然
- You let her have it? - Bigtime.
- 我希望她觉得自己很蠢 - 非常难堪
- I hope she felt foolish. - It was painful.
好了,乖
Okay. Be good.
要小心.好好看家
Be safe. Keep an eye on the old place.
包在我身上
I got it all covered.
作好准备
Here we go.
只靠你和我
It's just you and me.
你是说难道还有别人?
You mean there's someone else?
作战开始!
Get ready to rumble! Play ball!
(游泳池)
(弹床)
防不胜防
The old switcheroo.
- 来啊 - 大显身手的时间到了!
- Come on. - It's showtime!
那要是真的,我就是老鹰了
If those are real, I'm an eagle.
封锁街道
Block the street.
- 你好 - 嗨,我是凯伦·普鲁伊特
- Hello. - Hi, it's Karen Pruitt.
您能帮我去看看艾历克斯吗?
Could you check on Alex for me?
我正要出门
I'm just going out.
我在上班脱不开身
I'm at work and in a bind.
呃,多久?
Well, how long?
不超过一小时
It wouldn't be for more than an hour.
好,不包括煮饭
All right. No cooking.
找赫斯太太..
"Call Mrs.Hess.
她退休了,在家还能有什么事干?
She's retired, what else could she possibly be doing?"
临时保姆!
Babysitter!
他们过节时邀请过我?当然没有!
Would they invite me to their house for holiday eggnog? Of course not!
看谁出来了
Look who woke up from her nap.
坏蛋距离30码,正走过来
Crooks at 30 yards and closing.
好戏上场
Let the party begin.
下午好,我们刚搬来这里
Good afternoon. We just moved into your neighborhood.
想要什么,钮扣吗?
What do you want, a button?
我们有一个包裹,但司机搞错了
A package was to be delivered to us, but the driver got confuse,
可能送到了这里
perhaps he brought it here.
不,这儿没有任何东西送来
Nope, they didn't bring anything here.
快递公司说没人应门包裹留在车房
The delivered company said no one answered the door and the driver left it in the garage.
有时他们将包裹放在后门
Sometimes they leave stuff at the back door.
你为何关门?
Why are you closing the door?
我将面包留在三藩市
I left my heart in San Francisco.
小鬼将屋子关得密不透风
It looks like he has the place locked up pretty tight.
(危险有电 小心)
杰尼根,一定很好玩
Jernigan, I think I'm going to enjoy this.
好久没玩过小孩子的玩意了
It's been a long time since I was a kid.
快忘了小孩子有多蠢
You forget how incredibly stupid they are.
你小心
You be careful.
小孩子害怕时,他们会尿裤子
When kids get scared, they wet their pants.
昂格尔先生?
Mr.Unger?
我没事
I'm all right.
昂格尔先生,你在干什么?
Mr.Unger, what are you doing?
别碰那些线,有电
Don't touch the yarn. It's wired.
那小孩到处布设陷阱
Kid's got the place booby-trapped.
别大意
Make no assumptions.
小心垫子
Watch the mat.
这孩子很聪明,你试过开门吗?
This boy is clever. Have you tried the door?
还没有
Not yet.
你仔细看好我给你提示
Let me point something out to you.
我没留意
Missed that.
别走近
Stand clear.
也许他不是那么聪明
Maybe he's not so clever after all.
对,今天表现失常
Yeah, I think we're just having an off day.
给你一个忠告..
A thought for you to consider:
通过机场时..
At airport security..
千万别拿错行李
..make sure you have the right package.
我希望你不会..
I certainly hope that you're not..
喜欢对街那个男孩
..fond of that little boy across the street.
我会开着门
I'll leave this open.
新鲜空气对你有益
Fresh air will be good for you.
自以为很聪明?你个小鬼!
Think you're smart? You little brat!
昂格尔,情况如何?
Unger, what's your status?
抬头
Heads up.
- 怎么回事? - 我不知道
- How'd that happen? - I don't know.
哎哟
Ouch.
你们被书砸中?
You got hit with a book?
书,好多书
Books. Plural.
一大箱的书
A trunk full of books..
接着是哑呤,我连中两次,你个笨女人
..then a set of weights. I got hit twice, you dumb broad.
对不起,昂格尔先生.我不会给那孩子吓怕
Excuse me, Mr.Unger. I didn't get taken down by an infant.
我们想不到他会反击
We didn't anticipate the defense.
我由正面进去
I'll go in the front.
昂格尔先生,你由北面进去
Mr.Unger, you take the north side.
爱丽丝,你由南面进去
Alice, you take the south side.
杰尼根先生在哪儿?
Where is Mr.Jernigan?
请注意,旅客们
Attention, travelers.
所有前往芝加哥的航班因风雪暂停
All flights to Chicago continue to be delayed due to severe weather.
请等待进一步通知
Please stand by for further details.
(祝君快乐)
(强力地板胶)
你跑得掉但躲不掉,小子
You can run but you can't hide, junior.
惊喜
Surprise.
真没用
What a loser.
找到他了!
I got him!
你死定了,小子
You are dead, kid.
事有转机
Now things are looking up.
逮到你了!
Gotcha!
再见
See you.
喔,喔,喔
Well, well, well.
想整我没那么容易,小子
Nice try, kid.
爱丽丝?
Alice?
我下来了
I'm coming down.
杰尼根先生!昂格尔先生!
Mr.Jernigan! Mr.Unger!
欢迎
Welcome.
你剪了头发?
You got a haircut?
你可以了吗?
Are you almost done in there?
别来惹我
Don't start with me.
我等你
I'll wait.
我们走
Let's move.
- 什么臭味? - 闭嘴
- What stinks? - Shut up.
喂?
Hello?
你上气不接下气,有什么事吗?
You're out of breath. Something wrong?
不,没事
No, everything's fine.
我好担心,天气很坏
I'm so worried. The weather is terrible.
我现在回家
I'm gonna come home now.
不,不,别急,真的.不用赶回来,妈妈
No, no, take your time, really. Don't come home, Mom.
妈妈,你先去学校接斯坦和莫莉
Pick up Stan and Molly from school.
真的?
Are you sure?
嗯,我在跟赫斯太太下中国象棋
Yeah, I'm playing Chinese checkers with Mrs.Hess.
你没吸烟吧?
You're not smoking?
没有.我得走了,赫斯太太不喜欢等
No. I gotta go. Mrs.Hess gets nutty when you make her wait.
好,别耍赖
Okay, play fair.
不会的
Always.
勇敢的小家伙
What a brave little fellow.
杰尼根先生
Mr.Jernigan.
- 客厅没有人 - 好
- Living room clear. - Good.
厨房什么也没有
Nothing in the kitchen.
杰尼根先生,跟着我,慢点
Mr.Jernigan, follow me. Slowly.
去,多丽丝
Go, Doris.
昂格尔先生,走
Mr.Unger, go ahead.
掩护他,我监视楼梯
Cover him, I'll cover the stairs.
我来找你了,小矮子,来找你报仇了
I'm coming for you, shorty, to pay you back..
为了你给我受的罪
..for all the misery you caused me.
昂格尔先生,你干什么?
Mr.Unger, what are you doing?
孩子在衣橱里
Kid's in the closet.
在我捉他前,先吓吓他
Scaring him a little, just before I grab him.
看谁在门后面!
And behind door number one!
毛巾
Towels.
我看到门关上
I saw this door close.
白痴!
Idiot!
我会撒谎吗?
Would I make it up?
为什么?有意思吗?我们有佣金吗?
Why? What's the point? We working on commission here?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
- 华盛顿街的普鲁伊特太太? - 怎么?
- Mrs.Pruitt from Washington Street? - Yes?
斯塔基探员,联邦调查局
Agent Stuckey, FBI.
我来找你儿子谈谈
I came to talk to your son.
你打电话给空军说遥控车内有电脑芯片?
You called about a computer chip in a remote-control car?
没有
No.
哦,天啊,是艾历克斯.是我另一个儿子.发生什么事?
Oh, God. It's Alex. It's my other son. What's happened?
他可能有危险
He may be in danger.
他不在这里,他在家
He's not here. He's at home.
我们走
Let's move.
为何他有危险?
Why is he in danger?
她问你问题,先生
She asked you a question, sir.
我不方便谈,孩子
I'm not at liberty to discuss it, son.
你说的人是我小弟弟
The "it" you're referring to is my little brother.
我们相信他取得了一个机密电脑芯片
We thing he intercepted a top-secret electronic device..
是被从防御部门偷走的
..stolen from a Defense Dept. Contractor..
罪犯替北朝鲜恐怖组织工作
..by criminals working for a North Korean terrorist organization.
杰尼根先生,过来
Mr.Jernigan, come here.
绿眼女郎,海的女儿
Green-eyed lady, ocean lady
踏浪而来
Moving every breaking wave that comes
上,多丽丝,上!
Go, Doris, go!
绿眼女郎,海的女儿
Green-eyed lady, ocean lady
踏浪而来
Moving every breaking wave that comes
绿眼女郎,海的女儿
Green-eyed lady, lovely lady
迎着阳光漫步而来
Strolling slowly towards the sun
抱歉,查理
Sorry, Charlie.
你今天运气不太好
This just ain't your day.
闭嘴
Shut up.
- 什么? - 别动
- What? - Don't move.
爱丽丝?
Alice?
别..
Don't..
..动
..move.
爱丽丝?
Alice?
- 干嘛?爱丽丝? - 嘘!
- What? Alice? - Shh!
爱丽丝?
Alice?
好极
Excellent.
快逃,小矮子,快逃!
Run, shorty, run!
快,多丽丝
Come on, Doris.
那小子!
The kid!
多丽丝,快来!
Doris, come on!
死小子!
You little brat!
我捉到他了!
I got him!
你打我要害
You smacked my winkie.
如果你常换内裤,也许就不会有老鼠!
If you changed your shorts, maybe you wouldn't have rats in your pants!
我受够了!
Scraggy little rug rat!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
留在这里,多丽丝
Stay here, Doris.
呀
Yikes.
发射!
Fire!
他一直在监视我们.他用摄像机监视我们
He's been watching us the whole time. He had a camera on us.
你在那里找不到我,你个大笨蛋,无法无天的蠢货!
You won't find me up there, you big, dumb, law-breaking knuckleheads!
他在外面
He's outside.
认得这个吗?
Recognize this?
他怎么出去的?
How'd he get outside?
你们也一样出去
The same way you will get outside.
跳!快!
Jump! Go!
别推
Don't push.
是弹床.你跳到弹床上
It's a trampoline. You're jumping onto a trampoline.
你不跟我们一起跳吗?
I presume you won't be joining us?
- 不,我在这里掩护你们,快! - 真让人安慰
- No, I'll be covering you. Go! - How comforting.
他要逃了!
He's getting away!
小菜一碟
This is a snap.
跳!
Go!
冷.非常冷
Cold. Very cold.
(阁楼)
原来如此
Of course.
我来了,小家伙
Here I come, you little brat.
哎哟
Ouch.
赫斯太太!
Mrs.Hess!
赫斯太太
Mrs.Hess.
你没事,我来了
You're okay. I'm here now.
呃..
Well..
你是艾历克斯,对吧?
..it's Alex, isn't it?
今天你要学到..
Today you learn something.
当好市民要付出代价
There is a price to be paid for being a good citizen.
因为你的热忱想救邻居,而掉入我的陷阱
In your zeal to aid your neighbor, you stepped into one of my traps.
芯片不在这里!
The chip's not here!
能让赫斯太太进屋去吗?她很老又很冷
Can Mrs.Hess go inside? She's very old and very cold.
拜托?
Please?
给我芯片
Give me the chip.
芯片不属于你,不是你的
It doesn't belong to you. It's not yours.
芯片,小子.给我芯片
The chip, son. Give me the chip.
- 那也不属于你 - 什么?
- That doesn't belong to you either. - What?
那不是你的枪
That's not your gun.
这才是你的枪
This is your gun.
骗到你了!
Gotcha!
- 来,坐下,赫斯太太 - 谢谢你,艾历克斯
- Here, sit down, Mrs.Hess. - Thank you, Alex.
现在该喝碗汤,喜欢什么汤?
These are times that call for soup. Any favorites?
谢谢,不用了
Thank you. I'm fine.
你知道,赫斯太太..
You know, Mrs.Hess..
外面真的很冷.对老人来说你真壮健
..it's really cold outside. You're a pretty tough old bird.
你真是个细心的好孩子
And you're a very sweet young man.
我以前从没留意到
I just never took the time to notice.
不只你没留意
You're not alone in that.
约翰逊,威廉姆斯,到后面去
Johnson, Williams. Go around back.
别动!
Freeze!
怎么动?
You gotta be kidding.
艾历克斯
Alex.
妈妈!
Mom!
你当着警察的面抱我还亲我
You're hugging and kissing me in front of the cops.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
真抱歉我没相信你
I'm so sorry I didn't listen to you.
精采
This is very cool.
伙计,你真个英雄了
Bud, you're a hero.
- 你是艾历克斯? - 是的
- Are you Alex? - Yeah.
斯塔基探员,联邦调查局
Agent Stuckey, FBI.
芯片在这里
Here's the chip.
街对面有个长者..
There's a senior citizen across the street..
她需要热汤和医生去看看她的脚
..who needs some soup and a doctor to look at her feet.
游泳池有两个家伙,地下室有个女的
There's two guys in our pool and a woman in our basement.
另一个跑了
The other one's gone.
是他吗?
Is this him?
对
Yep.
我追捕这家伙七年了
Seven years, I've been after this guy.
每次都让他逃脱
He always manages to slip away.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 只有这三个人 - 你们老大在哪儿?
- It's just the three. - Where's your boss?
- 把他们带走! - 是,长官.走吧,冰棍
- Get them out of here! - Yes, sir. Let's go, popsicle.
快点
Come on.
露西,我回家了!
Lucy, I'm home!
你打什么主意,猴子屁股?
What's on your mind, monkey butt?
坏,坏,勒罗伊·布朗
Bad, bad, Leroy Brown.
休士顿,出了问题
Houston, we have a problem.
倒数..
Counting down in..
..5,4,3,2..
..five, four, three, two..
给你
Take it.
两片,否则免谈
Double or nothing.
我只有一片
I only have one.
点火
We have ignition.
表演时间!
It's showtime!
我一会儿就到.好,再见
I'll be there in just a minute. Okay, bye.
门前没铲雪的中古型房子
It's the Tudor with the Christmas lights in the driveway..
就是那一家
..that hasn't been shoveled.
那家,就那儿
That one, right there.
你长过水痘吗?
Have you ever had the chickenpox?
我长水痘时赫伯特·胡佛还在白宫呢!
I had the chickenpox when Herbert Hoover was in the White House.
你们好
Hello.
爸爸!
Dad!
嘿,过来
Hey, come here.
让我看看.你看来还很好
Let's see. You don't look any worse for the wear.
他们斗不过我
They couldn't touch me.
电脑公司送给艾历克斯奖金
The computer company with the boosted chip is giving Alex a reward.
有六位数的奖金,利害
It's a six-figure sum, which is extremely cool.
那你有礼物给我吗?
So did you bring me anything?
当然有
As a matter of fact, I did.
过来
Come here.
你会遥控吗?
Think you can drive that?
我想没问题
I think we can handle it.
先生们,发动引擎
Gentlemen, start your engines.
360度回转!
360! 360!
老鼠坠车!
Rat overboard!
笑一笑
Say cheese.